# **William Hall**

Phone: (803)414-9580 | E-mail: WHall22@outlook.com Website: https://whhall.github.io

# **Professional Summary**

Successful graduate of Midlands Technical College with an Associates in Computer Technology and recipient of the TechHire Front End Programming Scholarship. Six years of customer service and two years of web development. Passionate about learning, solving problems, and building positive customer experiences with intuitive designs.

### **Technical Skills**

Programming: Java, MySQL, HTML, CSS Advanced, JavaScript, AJAX, Bootstrap 4, SEO

Software: Microsoft Office 365, Adobe Photoshop, GIMP, Visual Studio, Coldfusion Builder

Operating Systems: Windows 7/8.1/10, Ubuntu Linux, Android, IOS

#### Work Experience

# Department of Education, Columbia, SC **UI/UX Developer**

August 2019 – Present

- Developing UI/UX standards for all department web applications.
- Designing responsive web templates using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap 4.
- Analyzing requirements and implementing solutions based on departmental needs.
- Formatting and editing media and infographics for web usage.
- Communicating with team members in daily SCRUM sessions, Outlook, and Teams.

# 116 Wine and Espresso, Columbia, SC Bartender/Manager

June 2018 – April 2019

- Created a unique experience for all guests with an unmatched level of customer service.
- Managed all monetary transactions throughout establishment.
- Coordinated teams of five or more dining room and kitchen staff.
- Increased revenue using soft sales and upselling techniques.
- Educated in mixology and wine with emphasis on European varietals.

# Thirsty Fellow, Columbia, SC

November 2013 – June 2018

#### Waiter

- Excelled at developing relationships with customers and creating repeat business.
- Upheld high level of organization while multitasking in a fast-paced environment.
- Maintained professional composer and awareness under high pressure.
- Voted best waiter in Columbia by Free Times 2014.

#### **Education**

## Midlands Technical College, Columbia, SC

Associate of Applied Science in Computer Technology Aug. 2017 – May. 2019

TechHire Front End Programming Scholarship May 2019 – Aug. 2019

University of South Carolina, Columbia, SC

Bachelor of Science in Information Science

Expected Graduation May 2021